#### DATA ANALYST · MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEE

Leuven, Belaium

□ (+32)486 62 50 78 | bisschopslode@gmail.com | • LodeBisschops | • lode-bisschops

## Summary\_

Current student artificial intelligence at top university KULeuven finishing in July 2022. With more than 2 years of work experience with databases and data analysis. I'm easy going and love to problem-solve challenging tasks, learn new technologies and interface with different departments.

## **Education**

#### **Katholieke Universiteit Leuven**

Leuven, Belgium

MASTERS OF COMPUTER SCIENCE: ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

2020 - 2022

- Belgium's highest-ranked university
- Elective courses: Uncertainty in Artificial Intelligence | Advanced Programming Languages for A.I. | Artificial Neural Networks and Deep Learning | Data Mining | Genetic Algorithms and Evolutionary Computing | Principles of Machine Learning | Distributed Systems | Software Architecture

University of Hasselt Hasselt, Belgium

**BACHELORS OF COMPUTER SCIENCE** 

2016 - 2020

- In depth understanding of Python, Java, C++ and C
- · Familiar with: Prolog, Javascript, cloud based solutions, relational and non-relational databases.
- · Strong background in Mathematics, Statistics and Software Engineering

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**FibriCheck**Hasselt, Belgium

 Data Analyst
 Feb. 2020 - May. 2022

- Created an automated data market using data pipelines and cloud computing infrastructure.
- · Constructed data visualisations.
- · Provided actionable insights and calculated key performance indicators.
- · Leaded my own project.
- In depth understanding of NoSQL data aggregation through research.
- · Created data insights using python and jupyter notebooks.
- Interfaced with marketing to understand their needs.
- Clearly documented my work and educated colleagues at the end of my contract.

TeamHypeCoaching Flanders, Belgium

STRENGTH COACH

late 2020 - Jun. 2021

- · Worked a company with 2 friends, Providing online strength coaching for 40 athletes.
- · Progress analysis using excel automation.

**Le Notariat**Westerlo, Belgium

WAITER AND HOSPITALITY

Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2021

• Serving at a Gault & Millau selected cocktail bar, serving guests as a hospitable host.

### Research\_

### **Exploring Deceptive affiliate Marketing within Facebook**

Leuven, Belgium

MASTER THESIS

**BACHELOR THESIS** 

2021-2022

- Researching malicious advertisements within Facebook and how to detect them.
- Finding patterns within large datasets using SQL, python and MongoDB.
- Gathering data with web-scraping tools in remote containerized applications using Kubernetes.

#### Aggregating Data for Statistical Analysis in MongoDB Atlas.

Hasselt, Belgium

• Compared different database technologies for data aggregation.

Feb. 2020 - Jun. 2020

- Explored different ways to aggregate data in an unstructured NoSQL database.
- Set up a real-time dashboard for basic performance indicators.

# **Extracurricular Activity**

April 17, 2022 Bisschops Lode · Résumé

### **Hermes - fraternity of economics**

Hasselt

PLEDGEMASTER 2019

- Organised social events for new students.
- Helped at the job fair.
- Participated in biweekly meetings.Organised more than 10 large student parties.

# References \_\_\_\_\_

Contact me for reference letters.